VIVIAN UFONDU

PROFILE

Diligent User support technicians with 3+ years of experience in supporting computer users experiencing difficulties with computer hardware and with computer applications and communications software. To work with existing staff and facilities, contributing to the best of my ability and quota, improving organizational objectives, and achieving organizational goals and targets.

PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATES

- Introduction to ServiceNow Fulfillers.
- Advance to ServiceNow Fulfillers.
- Certificate in computer utilization.
- Oracle certified associate, oracle 11g administration-2011.
- Certificate in Linux & oracle database administration.
- Certificate of participation at the workshop on Health advantage.
- Standard First-Aid Certification.

SKILLS

- Fluency in English speaking, writing, listening, and reading.
- Good interpersonal and problem-solving skills.
- Strong time management and organizational skills.
- Good use of Microsoft Office tools.
- Self-motivated and target-oriented.
- Ability to work effectively in a team.

EXPERIENCE

Advanced AI Data Trainer. January 2023 - Present.

Company: Invisible Technologies, Inc. San Francisco, CA, USA.

Responsibilities:

- Generating examples of ideal conversations, acting as both User and Al.
- Collecting sources, helping it read large swaths of humanity's documented knowledge and distinguish between what is presented as fact vs context vs patterns of behavior.
- Continuously evaluate the AI according to training methods.
- Creating models that will best be used to train, test, and correct the Al.

AIM Support Specialist (3-month Contract).

October 2022 - December 2023

Company: 3sHealth Saskatchewan -Saskatoon, SK

Responsibilities:

- Provided technical support to over 200 users, ensuring smooth operation of computer systems and resolving hardware and software issues promptly.
- Maintained an up-to-date problems and solutions log, which served as a valuable resource for the IT team and reduced repeat issues by 30%.
- Tier 1 support employee level via inbound calls, email, or case management (ServiceNow).
- Tier 1 supporting staff with the use of online scheduling.
- Provide desktop support and resolve tickets on the ticketing system.
- Team lead providing
- Supervised a team of junior technical support analysts, providing guidance and mentorship to improve



VIVIAN UFONDU

- their skills and performance.
- Manually create Return to Work and Accommodation information into Oracle and other Data Entry.
- Demonstrated strong attention to detail and the ability to work under pressure, successfully managing multiple tasks and meeting tight deadlines.
- Collaborated with the IT team to implement network security measures, resulting in a 25% reduction in security incidents.

Customer Relations Associate

October 2021 - September 2022

Company: HGS Canada Inc-Saskatoon, SK

Responsibilities:

- Response to customer queries on billing, price plan inclusion, payment, and other products and services; and always aim to address queries the first time the customer is calling about it.
- Utilize 4 to 8 applications simultaneously, Integrated Customer Management (ICM), Voice ID, Telli,
 V21, etc. In answering customers' queries.
- Document customer's queries, information, and resolution give accurately to ensure continuity of support in the future.
- Upgrade product and process knowledge by reading the alerts in NOVA, always being online in the internal communication tools such as work email, spark, and chat groups, and attending huddles, classroom, and/or e-learning sessions.
- Educate the customer about their service inclusions, especially those they may not be aware of, and encourage them to use self-service portals.
- Follow the contact handling policy- always answer calls in a professional tone and manner, follow work schedules, maintain reliability, meet performance metrics, always be open to feedback and coaching, and strive to keep the coaching attainment plan on track.

Data scientist.

November 2012 - August 2021

Company: Ecart Internet Services Nigeria.

Responsibilities:

- Provide business systems, network, and Internet support to users in response to identified difficulties using Windows, Android, and IOS systems.
- Consult user guides, technical manuals, and other documents to research and implement solutions.
- Collect, organize, and maintain a problems and solutions log for use by other technical support analysts.
- Use Zendesk to manage and document daily reported issues in a bug-tracking system.
- Resolve customer complaints via phone, email, or social media.
- Answer in-person or on-the-phone, inquiries from customers.
- Working with the ticketing system.
- Tier 1 desktop support to administrative staff and customers.

VOLUNTARY WORK EXPERIENCE

Personal Care Worker

July 28 2022 - July 28 2022.

Company: Aspira Riverbend Crossing Memory Care - Regina, SK **Responsibilities:**

- Assistance with bathing, dressing, and grooming.
- Tidying, bed-making, and laundry service.



VIVIAN UFONDU

EDUCATION

- Saskatchewan Council, Canada | July 2022 St. John Ambulance Saint-Jean in Personal Care Worker Class #: 76-6350-000-SK60-260722-4465.
- National Open University of Nigeria, Nigeria | January 2013 to August 2014.
 Post Graduate Diploma in Information Technology.
- Federal University of Technology Owerri, Nigeria | September 2004 September 2010.
 Bachelors in Physics.